https://www.ovationtv.com/privacy-policy/

Inside the Actors Studio
Inside the Actors Studio (Classic Episodes)
Channel Finder
Find out what channel Ovation is on in your area.
TV Service Provider
Find out what channel Ovation is on in your area.
TV Service Provider
Social
Watch
Privacy Policy
This is the Privacy Policy for all web sites or mobile web sites owned or operated by Ovation LLC (“Ovation”), including the web site currently located at www.ovationtv.com (the "Site"), any applications (e.g., iPhone applications, iPad applications, Android applications, etc.) offered by Ovation, and any other applications, interactive features, blogs, social media platforms, widgets and resources offered by Ovation through traditional Internet websites, mobile devices or other platforms (all of which are collectively referred to as the “Services”). Your privacy is important to us and we have prepared this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use, and protect Volunteered Information (defined below) and Logged Information (defined below) when you use the Services and your choices for managing your information preferences. By using the Services, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use.
1. Managing Information Preferences
We will not disclose Volunteered Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes without your consent. If, after providing consent, you want to opt out of having your Volunteered Information disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes, please let us know by sending us an email at privacy@ovationtv.com.
You may review, correct, update, or change your Volunteered Information at any time by contacting us at:
Ovation LLC
Attn: Robert Rader
12910 Culver Blvd., Suite J
Los Angeles, CA 90066
Email: privacy@ovationtv.com
2. Information You Choose to Submit
We may collect information that personally identifies you, such as your name, address, telephone number, email address, or other data which can be reasonably linked to such information ("Volunteered Information") only if you choose to share such information with us. For example, you may be required to provide us with certain Volunteered Information to register with the Services, sign up for certain Services (such as text messages, mobile phone applications, and other communications services), subscribe to a newsletter, enter sweepstakes, contests, or other promotions, and at other times. The decision to provide this information is optional; however, if you decide not to register or provide such information, you may not be able to use certain features of the Services.
3. Information We Automatically Collect
We automatically collect certain information ("Logged Information") to help us understand how our users use the Services. Like most Web sites, we automatically collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files may include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), the Web browser you used to visit the Services, the time you visited the Services, which Web pages you visited on the Services, and other anonymous usage data.
4. Cookies and Web Beacons; Do Not Track
We may use cookies (a small file containing a string of characters that uniquely identifies your Web browser) and Web beacons (an electronic file placed within a Web site that monitors usage). We may use cookies and Web beacons to improve the quality of the Services. Most Web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your Web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, certain features of the Services may not work if you delete or disable cookies. Certain of our Service Providers (defined below) may use cookies and Web beacons in connection with the services they perform on our behalf.
We may work with third party advertising companies that may use information about your use of the Services in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you on the Service and on third-party websites or to serve ads promoting other Ovation products and services. From the Services, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as web beacons or pixel tags. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that a third-party ad serving company may collect from you. For more information about ad cookies and companies that provide users the ability to “opt-out” of the collection of information from such cookies, please click here: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service of Google, Inc. (“Google”), to collect and summarize data regarding usage of the Services. Google uses cookies to obtain this information. We use the information obtained from Google Analytics to improve the Services. To learn more about Google Analytics and Google’s privacy practices, please visit: www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/. For information on how to opt out of data collection by Google Analytics visit: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en
Our Services do not respond to web browser “do not track” signals or other mechanisms that provide consumers the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of Logged Information about an individual consumer’s online activities over time. Visit www.donottrack.us to find out more about “do not track.”
5. How We Use Your Information
We do not sell your information to third parties, and we will not otherwise disclose your information to third parties, without your express permission or as expressly disclosed in this Privacy Policy.
We use your information (both your Volunteered Information and Logged Information) for internal purposes only, such as to send service notifications, to customize the content you see, to fulfill your requests for products and services, to improve the Services, to conduct research, to solicit your feedback and input about the Services, and to provide more relevant products, services, and advertisements on or through the Services. Volunteered Information and Logged Information may be combined with data collected from other sources so that we may further improve the relevance of products, services, and advertisements offered on or through the Services.
From time to time, we may establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours ("Service Providers"). For example, we may contract with Service Providers to provide certain services, such as shipping and fulfillment, data management services, Web hosting and Web development. We provide our Service Providers with the information reasonably necessary for them to perform these services. Each Service Provider must agree (a) to implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information involved in order to protect your information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure and (b) not to retain, use, or disclose the information for any purpose other than for the specific purpose of performing the services for us, or as otherwise permitted by law.
We may use, and disclose to third parties, certain aggregated Logged Information regarding the Services (e.g., number of visits, page views, number of registered members who reside in a particular geographic location, etc.). However, such information does not identify you individually.
We may share your information with entities controlling, controlled by, or under common control with Ovation. In the event that Ovation is merged, sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our assets, we may disclose or transfer your information in connection with such transaction.
In certain instances, we may disclose your information when we believe it is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against persons or entities in order to protect Ovation or our users or when we believe that the law or legal process requires such disclosure.
6. Public Areas and External Sites
Please be advised that whenever you voluntarily post information to any community or interactive areas of the Services, such information can and may be accessed by the public. This means that any person or entity with access to such information can potentially use it for any purpose, including sending unsolicited communications.
The Services may contain links to, or advertisements about, third-party websites, applications or other properties (“Other Sites”). Other Sites may also reference, advertise, or link to the Services. We do not endorse or sponsor Other Sites and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of Other Sites. The practices described in this Privacy Policy do not apply to information gathered by third parties through Other Sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of each and every website that you visit.
7. Third-Party Services
Through the Services, you may elect to access third-party services and applications, such as Facebook and other social networks. When you do so, you may be able to import information from those other services and applications and share content with those services. Some of those third-party services may also provide us with information from your accounts which may enable us to enhance and personalize your use of the Services. If you choose to enable or use such third-party services or applications on the Services, the information you share with such third-party services and applications will be subject to their privacy policies and your privacy settings for such services. You also may be able to control or block such sharing by changing your privacy settings in such services or applications.
8. Security
Information that we collect is stored on servers that Ovation manages, using standard security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information in an effort to protect information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect information transmitted on or through the Services, we cannot and do not guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit on or through the Services, and you do so at your own risk.
9. Children’s Privacy Statement
We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records.
10. Processing in the United States
The Services are operated solely in the United States. Your information and communications may be transferred to and maintained on servers or databases located outside your state, province, or country. By providing any information to us, all users, including, without limitation, users in the member states of the European Union, Canada or elsewhere outside of the United States, fully understand and unambiguously consent to this Privacy Policy. If you are located outside of the United States, the laws of the United States may not be as protective of your privacy as those in your location. By using our Properties, you agree that the collection, use, transfer, and disclosure of your Volunteered Information and communications will be governed by the applicable laws in the United States.
11. California Residents
These additional notices are provided under the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) and apply to California residents in addition to the other provisions of this Privacy Policy.
As described above, we do not sell your information to any third party.
If you are a California resident, you have the following rights:
• You may request, no more than two times each year, that we disclose to you the following for the 12-month period preceding our receipt of your request:
o The categories of personal information we have collected about you;
o The categories of sources from which the personal information is collected;
o The business or commercial purpose for collecting your personal information;
o The categories of third parties with whom we share personal information; and
o The specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you.
• You may request that we delete any personal information that we have collected from or about you. Except as provided under the CCPA, we will delete such information in response to your request.
To make a request, you may contact us via mail, email, or phone:
Ovation LLC
Attn: General Counsel
12910 Culver Blvd., Suite J
Los Angeles, CA 90066
Email: privacy@ovationtv.com
In order to respond to your requests, we may need to verify your identity. We will not discriminate against you in the provision of the Services in response to your exercise of these privacy rights. We will respond to your request within 45 days of receipt of your request, after verification, unless we need additional time, in which case we will let you know and may extend the period an additional 45 days as permitted by the CCPA.
We collect information in the following categories and for the following purposes:
Category
Business and Commercial Purposes:
Identifiers such as a real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, and email address
·      Auditing related to a current interaction with the consumer and concurrent transactions, including, but not limited to, counting ad impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning and quality of ad impressions, and auditing compliance;
·      Detecting security incidents, protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, and prosecuting those responsible for that activity;
·      Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality; Short-term, transient use, including, but not limited to, the contextual customization of ads;
·      Performing services, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments;
·      Internal research for technological development and demonstration;
·      Verifying or maintaining the quality of the Services and to improve, upgrade, or enhance the Services.
Internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing history and information regarding an interaction with an Internet website, application, or advertisement
·      Auditing related to a current interaction with the consumer and concurrent transactions, including, but not limited to, counting ad impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning and quality of ad impressions, and auditing compliance;
·      Detecting security incidents, protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, and prosecuting those responsible for that activity;
·      Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality; Short-term, transient use, including, but not limited to, the contextual customization of ads;
·      Performing services, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments;
·      Internal research for technological development and demonstration;
·      Verifying or maintaining the quality of the Services and to improve, upgrade, or enhance the Services.
Geolocation Data
·      Auditing related to a current interaction with the consumer and concurrent transactions, including, but not limited to, counting ad impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning and quality of ad impressions, and auditing compliance;
·      Detecting security incidents, protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, and prosecuting those responsible for that activity;
·      Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality; Short-term, transient use, including, but not limited to, the contextual customization of ads;
·      Performing services, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments;
·      Internal research for technological development and demonstration;
·      Verifying or maintaining the quality of the Services and to improve, upgrade, or enhance the Services.
Privacy Policy Changes
Ovation may, in its sole and absolute discretion, change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Ovation will post a copy of the Privacy Policy as changed on the Site. Your continued use of the Services constitutes your agreement to abide by the Privacy Policy as changed. If we make material changes to our Privacy Policy or practices, we may seek your affirmative consent to such changes. If you object to any such changes, your sole recourse shall be to cease using the Services.
Effective Date: January 1, 2020
Don’t miss the latest Ovation news
This field is required.
This field is required.
Sign Up
Thank you for joining our mailing list!
Error: Server responded with a 501. Please try again.
By signing up, you agree to receive occasional emails from Ovation TV. For more info, view our Privacy Policy
dismissing in 5...
